SAI SRI CHARAN +91 – 9880963316

polavarapucharan@hotmail.com

ABOUT ME

I Sai Sri Charan a versatile person in adopting new technologies in an ever-changing world and exuberant in working on new projects. I have one year and three months of experience in MERN Stack. I am familiar with developing APIs using node.js and React.js/Next.js for the frontend. I have worked with both SQL and NoSQL databases. For deployment, I have worked with AWS EC2, Heroku, and Netlify.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JAN 2021 - PRESENT

ASSOCIATE DEVELOPER, AT QUEST SUSTAINABLE SOLUTIONS PVT LTD.

- 1. Worked on B2C, B2B Front end web applications using React JS.
- 2. Worked on MERN Stack application for corporates to assess their current position on corporate sustainability.

JUN 2020 - OCT 2020

ASSOCIATE DEVELOPER, CEACS PVT LTD.

1. Worked on B2B web Application using Django Framework.

EDUCATION

FEB 2020 - NOV 2020

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT (MERN), ATTAINU

Full-stack web development using MERN stack

APR 2013 – APR 2017

B. TECH (E.C.E), GITAM UNIVERSITY

Graduation in Bachelor of Electronics and communication.

PROJECTS

SUS360° BENCHMARKER

- India's first self-service 360-degree benchmarking tool on Corporate Sustainability
- Developed with MERN and deployed on AWS

BIKE RENTAL WEB APPLICATION (MERN), ATTAINU

- Front end with React where user can select the available bikes with selected dates and place
- Backed end was developed with Nodejs and with MongoDB provides API's

SOCIAL MEDIA WEB APPLICATION (MERN), ATTAINU

- Front end with React where user can post their photos or videos add friends and chat with them.
- Backed end was developed with Nodejs and with MongoDB provides API's
- Using Pusher Service, the users can chat live.

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML, CSS, Python, Git, GitHub.
- MERN Stack JavaScript, MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, NextJS, REDUX.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Surfing on the web.
- Watching cryptocurrency news.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES



• Recognized as a Microsoft Certified Professional in DEC 2018.